the.me 2017-05-09

# Privacy Policy | THEME

At THEME ([www.the.me](http://the.me/)), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by [www.the.me](http://the.me/) and how it is used.

**The Bottom Line**

We hate spam as much as you do. If you subscribe to the RSS feed we will not spam you or sell your email address to anyone else. You can always unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of the article.

**Comments**

Comments submitted to this website are the responsibility of the commenter. We reserve the right to remove or edit comments at our discretion. Site URLs (if provided) are published along with comments. Email addresses are required with the submission of comments but are not disclosed, unless the commenter deliberately does so him/herself by entering the email address in the main comment box in addition to the box clearly labeled for the email address.

We reserve the right to delete any comments that we deem not beneficial to the readership. This includes but is not limited to comments containing profanity, self promotion, harassment, threats or spam of any sort.

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized staff of this site (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

**Log Files**

Like many other websites, [www.the.me](http://the.me/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information, are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

[www.the.me](http://the.me/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize webpage content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**External Links**

The website contains links to other websites not owned by the owner of this website. We will not, and cannot, control how your personal information is used on these other websites. Consult the privacy policies of the linked websites to see how they use your information

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.the.me](http://the.me/).

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.the.me](http://the.me/) and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/1348695?hl=en).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and Web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include, among others:

Google AdSense  
Media.net  
eBay  
Amazon  
B&H  
Adorama  
DigitalRev

These and possibly other third party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.the.me](http://the.me/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or Web beacons) may also be used by the third party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[www.the.me](http://the.me/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.the.me](http://the.me/)‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific Web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [the@the.me](mailto:the@the.me).

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
